Guide to the Robert Prosky papers, 1909-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: Photographs, 1930s-2005, (3 boxes)
  - Miscellaneous, Broadway Reunion 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, Characters at Kalt Tavern in Milwaukee n.d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, [In library with Ida Prosky and others], 2000s (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, Lucille Lortel 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous,[NBC 75th Anniversary], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, Negatives and slides 1950s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, The Helen Hayes Awards 1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, [Standby Broadway], 1950s (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, [White House photo, President Clinton and Robert Prosky], December 1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Modeling Jobs, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Personal, Childhood/Highschool, 1930s-1940s (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Personal, Family/Friends, 1950s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Personal, Miscellaneous slides, 1950s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Personal, Portraits, 1950s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Personal, Portraits, 1960s-2000s (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Personal, Portrait, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Personal, Portraits [Arena Stage shots to show versatility], 1960s (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Publicity, "People Weekly", September 3, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Publicity, [Russian Publication], 1970s (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Television, "Cheers", 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Television, "Hill Street Blues", 1984-1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Television, "Home Fires Burning", 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Television, "Veronica's Closet", 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Theatre, "All My Sons", 1950s (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Theatre, "The Caine Mutiny Court Marshall", 1960 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Theatre, "Awake and Sing", 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Theatre, "Camping with Henry and Tom", 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Theatre, "Caucasian Chalk Circle"[front], "National Health"[back], 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Theatre, "The Chemmy Circle", 1970 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Theatre, "The Cherry Orchard", 1960-1970 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Theatre, "Dear Charles", 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Theatre, "Death of a Salesman", 1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Theatre, "Democracy", 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Theatre, "Diaboliqle", 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Theatre, "A Doll's House", 1950s (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Theatre, "Front Page", 1958 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Theatre, "Galileo", 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Theatre, "Girls in 509", 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Theatre, "He Who Gets Slapped", 1965 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Theatre, "Hotel Paradiso"[front], "Sergeant Musgrave's Dance"[back], 1963-64, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Theatre, "Idiot's Delight", 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Theatre, "Inherit the Wind" [Russia], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Theatre, "Jabberwocky", 1960s (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Theatre, "La Fille Du Regiment" signed photo-Joan Sutherland n.d. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Theatre, "Lower Depths"[front], "National Health"[back], 1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Theatre, "The Madwoman of Chaillot", 1961 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Theatre, "Matchmaker", 1960s (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Theatre, "Middle of the Night", 1960s (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Theatre, "Millionaires", 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Theatre, "Misalliance", 1962 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Theatre, "Moon in the Yellow River"[front], "Time of Your Life"[back], 1962 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Theatre, "Mr. Welk and Jersey Jim"[front], "Three Men on a Horse"[back]; "Three Men on a Horse", 1959,1966; 1971 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Theatre, "No Time for Sergeants", 1960s (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Theatre, "Our Town"[front], "Leonce and Lena"[back]; "Our Town", 1974,1990-1991;1991 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Theatre, Photograph Album 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Theatre, "Picnic", 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Theatre, Portfolio Binder 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Theatre, "The Price", 1994 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Theatre, "Reluctant Debutante", 1950s (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Theatre, "Remny Baker", 1960s (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Theatre, "The Ruling Class", 1971 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Theatre, "Separate Tables", 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Theatre, [Shakespeare in Hollywood photo collage poster], 2003 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Theatre, "Streamers", 1970s (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Theatre, Unidentified 1950a-1960s (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Theatre, "A Walk in the Woods", 1988 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Theatre, "You Can't Take It With You", 1998 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Series 4: Audiovisual, 1960-2007, (2 boxes)
  Contains copies of Prosky's film and television appearances, particularly "Veronica's Closet." There are also copies of public serve announcements and commercials. Most of the media contained on VHS cassettes and reel-to-reel audio tapes. There are also DVD copies of speaking engagements at George Mason University and other locations.
  - Grandfather's Birthday, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    VHS, 18 minutes, color
  - Little Detroit Commercial (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Audio reel.
    Available on digital format.
  - Public Service TV Spot "Grade School", 1960 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Reel, 60 seconds, color.
  - Public Service Announcement "Shirley Safe Goes West" (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Reel, 60 seconds, color, U.S. Dept. of Agriculture Food Safety and Quality Service.
  - Show Demo (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Audio reel
  - Veronica's Closet - "Veronica's Blackout", 12 March 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    VHS, #466216, Final Viewing Cassette
  - Veronica's Closet - "Veronica's Bridal Shower", 2 April 1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    VHS, #466217, Final Viewing Cassette
  - Veronica's Closet - "Veronica's Man in a Suitcase", 9 April 1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    VHS, #466218, Final Viewing Cassette
  - Veronica's Closet - "Veronica's All Nighter", 16 April 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    VHS, #466219, Final Viewing Cassette
  - Veronica's Closet - "Veronica's Mole", 30 April 1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    VHS, #466220, Final Viewing Cassette
  - Veronica's Closet - "Veronica's Mole", 9 May 1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    VHS, #466221, Final Viewing Cassette
  - Warren Alder, Blacky's Restaurants, October 28, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Audio, 6 Demo spots, 7.5 IPS
  - Washington Monuments, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    VHS, 30 minutes
  - An American Daughter, April 25-June 1 2002/2003 season (Box 13, Folder 1)
    CD, Arena Stage press photos
  - An Evening with Robert Prosky DEMO, October 24, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    DVD, DEMO
  - An Evening with Robert Prosky, October 24, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    DVD, Tape 1, Harris Theatre GMU
  - An Evening with Robert Prosky, October 24, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    DVD, Tape 2, Harris Theatre GMU
  - An Evening with Robert Prosky, October 24, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    DVD, Clips for Lecture
  - Bob Grant Show about New York at Noon, May 16, [1985-1986] (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Audio cassette tape, WABC Talk Radio 77am
  - Crystal Cerise Lecture, ca. 2000s (Box 13, Folder 7)
    DVD
  - EPA-FEA "Gas Station", August 31, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Video reel, 60 seconds.
  - Harris Theatre tape, October 24, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Audio cassette tape, Tape 1
  - Harris Theatre tape, October 24, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Audio cassette tape, Tape 2
  - Robert Prosky-Faiga Levine Interview, April 1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Audio Cassette Tape, WTOP Radio
  - Oral History, November 8, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Unlabeled Audio Reel, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Series 5: Oversize, 1950s-2006, (2 boxes)
  The fifth series contains items too large for the other series. Included are photographs, scrapbooks, and posters documenting Prosky's professional career and personal life.
  - "Thief", 1981 (Oversize 14, Folder 1)
    Black binder with "Thief" label
  - Robert Prosky (Oversize 14, Folder 2)
    Black binder with Robert Prosky
  - Modeling Jobs, 1960s (Oversize 14, Folder 3)
    Photograph
  - "Legends of Golf Celebrity Pro-am" [Liberty Mutual], 1987 (Oversize 14, Folder 4)
    Photograph - Appearances
  - "The Hostage", 1972 (Oversize 14, Folder 5)
    Photograph - Theatre
  - The Television Movie Awards, 1985 (Oversize 14, Folder 6)
    Nomination for Best Supporting Actor in a Television Movie "Into Thin Air"
  - Headshot portfolio, 1980s (Oversize 14, Folder 7)
    Six different shots
  - Russian magazine, 1979 (Oversize 14, Folder 8)
    Interview page 37
  - Portraits, 1980s (Oversize 14, Folder 9)
    Three matted portraits
  - "The Price", August 23- September 23, 2006 (Oversize 14, Folder 10)
    Autographed film poster
  - "Inherit the Wind", September 26 - November 5, 2000 (Oversize 14, Folder 11)
    Production poster
  - Portrait photograph, ca.2000s (Oversize 14, Folder 12)
  - Early career scrapbook, 1950s (Oversize 15, Folder 1)
    Photographs, newspaper clippings, playbills
  - Theatre career scrapbook, 1950s-1980s (Oversize 15, Folder 2)
    Blue album with flowers on cover, photographs, newspaper clippings, playbills
  - "My Life With Bing", 1983 (Oversize 15, Folder 3)
    Autographed copy by Kathryn Crosby
- Series 6: Realia, 1998-2004, (1 box)
  Consists of objects from Prosky's professional career and personal life.
  - "Democracy", November 18, 2004 (Oversize 16, Folder 1)
    Paperweight
  - "Democracy", November 18, 2004 (Oversize 16, Folder 2)
    Miniature briefcase
  - Director's chair back support, n.d. (Oversize 16, Folder 3)
    Robert Prosky's name monogrammed on one side.
  - "Inherit the Wind", 2000 (Oversize 16, Folder 4)
    Ford's Theatre, Dog tags
  - P.B.A. Honorary Membership Award, 1988 (Oversize 16, Folder 5)
    Plaque
  - Roxborough High School 50th Class Reunion (Class of 1948), 1998 (Oversize 16, Folder 6)
    Souvenir bag